{
    "subject": "resource/Overture_to_The_Merry_Wives_of_Windsor",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_based_on_The_Merry_Wives_of_Windsor",
    "human_readable": "Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor is about The Merry Wives of Windsor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9855892062187195,
            "question": "What is the Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9739771485328674,
            "question": "Who likely composed the Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9698284864425659,
            "question": "Is there a musical piece titled 'Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9295967817306519,
            "question": "Which work of literature does the Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor relate to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8940909504890442,
            "question": "How does the Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor likely set the tone for the play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.836437463760376,
            "question": "Can you name other works by the composer of The Merry Wives of Windsor overture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7655301094055176,
            "question": "Why might a composer choose to write an overture for a work like The Merry Wives of Windsor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7166166305541992,
            "question": "What is the general theme or story of The Merry Wives of Windsor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.582055926322937,
            "question": "Are there any other musical pieces inspired by The Merry Wives of Windsor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30242249369621277,
            "question": "What kind of composition is an overture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor is about The Merry Wives of Windsor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6079_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other musical pieces inspired by The Merry Wives of Windsor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6079_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the general theme or story of The Merry Wives of Windsor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6079_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might a composer choose to write an overture for a work like The Merry Wives of Windsor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6079_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6079_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Overture to The Merry Wives of Windsor is about The Merry Wives of Windsor.\" This is evident from the descriptions in files `80.txt` and `15.txt`, which mention that the opera \"The Merry Wives of Windsor\" by Otto Nicolai features an overture, reinforcing the connection between the title of the overture and the source material."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}